How did you change? You went to the rally, they said
Как вы изменили вышли на митинг сказали
Kadyrov,
Кадыров
Hello, I greet you, you are
пё Здравствуйте приветствую тебя вы
an imperial,
имперец
I am a nationalist, oh, I am from the city of Khmelnitsky
я националист о о я из города Хмельницке
And what city are you from, Moscow, where are you from?
А Вы из какого города Москва вы откуда
This is the city of Khmelnitsky. I say,
будете это же город Хмельницкий Я говорю
Yes, it turns out you are a Russian nationalist,
Да вы получается вы русский националист
yes it
да
turns out this is a region, Well, Khmelnitsky
получается это область Ну Хмельницкая
region  Khmelnitsky region yes yes, and you are from
обла область Хмельницкая да да а а вы из
Khmelnitsky from Khmelnitsky itself Yes, and
Хмельницкого из самого Хмельницкого Да а
I understood the city, I understood everything, that is, you are like an
города я понял всё понял то есть вы типа
imperial
имперец
and a nationalist Yes, in yours  flag It’s
да националист Да вот на вашем флаге Я
just not the first time I’ve seen him there in the
его просто не первый раз вижу там в
middle,
середине
some kind of horseman is killing a dragon.
какой-то этот конник дракона убивает Это
Who is this prince? This is George
ж кто такой Что за князь это это Георгий
the Victorious and he’s there on the
Победоносец а он там на
flag. Well, you see, we are still the Heirs of the
флаге Ну понимаете мы вс-таки Наследники
Byzantine Empire. I understand, understand,
Византийской империи А понял понимайте
continuity exists. Ponia A  when, when,
преемственность существует Поня А когда
when did Russian nationalists
вот когда вот русские националисты
inherit the succession of the
унаследовали преемственность
Byzantine Empire, in what year can you
Византийской империи в каком году можете
remind me? I taught history poorly,
Напомнить Я плохо историю
listen, well, Russia has become
учил слушайте Ну Россия стала империей
empire back in the 15th century, as in the 15th century, the Russian Empire appeared in 1721 by decree of Peter I in the 10th century, yes. So, when did it become the successor to Byzantium, listen Well, plus or minus, the whole process actually began when we accepted Christianity. So you accepted Christianity. Well, we Rus' accepted Christianity with you We accepted Christianity styles yes But like you were the periphery of the Byzantine This is the Orthodox world of the periphery we were not the periphery  like the Periphery
были периферии как Периферия
Constantinople was yes this was right
Константинополь был да вот это был прям
about and Moscow so in short it’s already
о а Москва так это короче аж
far, far away from the entire Orthodox
далеко-далеко от всего православного
world Well listen damn pony I understand about the World Cup
мира Ну слушайте блин пони я понимаю о
you’re just talking about when when in
ЧМ вы говорите просто когда когда в
what year and who transferred the succession of the
какой год и кто передал преемственность
Byzantine Empire to Moscow Well
Византийской империи Москве Ну понимаете
you understand how  you could say different things, but
Вы как бы можете разные вещи говорить но
nevertheless, Russia
менее Россия -
adopted Christianity at
это переняла христианство в
8, adopted it well there, Serbia adopted it,
8 хорошо переняла там Сербия переняла
Greece adopted it, why not Greece
Греция переняла Почему не Греция
for example,
например
Greece adopted it earlier Yes, well, because the
Греция раньше переняла Да ну потому что
Greeks apparently could not defend their
греки видимо не смогли отстоять свою
identity. In the sense that the Greeks could not. You
идентичность В смысле греки не смогли Ты
understand now you’re talking, look. Dude
понимаешь сейчас говоришь смотри Чувак
you who ran. In short, once again
ты который бегал Короче ещё когда-то
somewhere in the forests like Mamotov,
где-то там в лесах типа на мамотов тем
nevertheless, nevertheless, who  ran to
не менее тем не менее кто бегал на
Turkey who ran back and forth again
Турцию кто бегал туда-сюда ещё раз
look at Byzantium to Byzantium who ran
смотри на Византию на Византию кто бегал
Greece there Serbia Bulgaria that's how many
Греция там Сербия Болгария вот сколько
Orthodox countries there are yes Why  would
есть православных стран да С чего бы
you be the successor to the Byzantine Empire since
вы преемник Византийской импе с того что
we are so simple
мы такие просто
Well,
Ну
you are simply God's Chosen Chosen
вы просто Богом Избранная Избранная
Country And I understood you And in what year God
страна А понял ви А в каком году вас Бог
chose you chose us Well, we have always been
избрал нас избрал Ну всегда мы были
Orthodox people, not when you
православными людьми не когда вот вы
were there before idols are shorter than you for
были раньше там идолы короче вас для
me from Russia  has a thousand-year history,
меня с Россия имеет тысячелетнюю историю
yes, that is, it will work out in my case When
да то есть получатся моём случае Когда
God Tell me When God chose When God
Бог Вот скажи Когда Бог избрал Когда Бог
said like the
сказал типа
chosen ones, we were chosen ones probably
избранные мы избранные наверное были
when we accepted Christianity And
когда когда мы приняли христианство А
what is your God’s
как как вашего Бога
name Jesus Christ is not that  the son of God and
зовут Иисус Христос не это сын Божий а
his
его
father Well, he is the Father son of the spirit He has three and yes
отца Ну он Отец сын дух У него три и да
Well, his father’s name is what the name is
Ну вот имени у его отца как как зовут
Yahweh of the Sabans not we we don’t have that we don’t
Яхве савов не мы у нас нет такого мы не
and wait PPP you the Bible
и подожди ППП ты Библию
Hush stt only the New Testament wait well the
Тишь стт только Новый Завет подожди ну
New Testament so New  The covenant is based
Новый Завет так Новый Завет основывается
on
на
what. Well, you sing in the new testament, there
чём Ну поете в новом завете там же
were more prophets there, that is, right
больше было пророков то есть правильно
Yes, well, look at the New New Testament, look,
Да Ну смотри Новый Новый Завет смотри
let's look so good, look at that, God in the
давай так хорошо смотри давай так Бог в
new testament and in  in the old testament Is this the
новом завете и в старом завете Это один
same God or are these some different
и тот самый Бог или это какие-то разные
gods Is this the same God one and the
боги Это один и тот же самый Бог один и
same God, that is, it turns out that
самый Бог да то есть получается что у
you and the Jews have the same God, we do not have the
вас и у евреев один и Той самый Бог не у
same God  let's say that in the
нас не один и тот же самый давай так в
old testament and in the new testament there is one and the
ветхом завете и в новом завете один и
same God Give for your health
тот самый Бог Дайте за ваше здоровье
first Oh give a godly deed to the
сначала О давай богоугодное дело
Russian
русскому
nationalist so look I'm
националист так то смотри Вот мне
interested, you have God in the new testament and
интересно вот у вас Бог в новом завете и
in the old  according to the covenant, these are the same, one and the
в старом завете это одинаковые один и
same God, not two different Gods.
тот же Бог не два разных Бога
The truth. Well, listen. Well, damn it, you’re an
Правда Ну слушайте Ну блин ну вы же
adult, one and the same
взрослый человек один и тот самый
God. Well, you already understand man.
Бог Ну вы человека уже Сами понимаете То
That is, it turns out that Moses and you have the
есть получается у Моисея и у вас один и
same God; the Jews don’t understand.
тот же самый Бог не понимаете евреи
they live according to the Old Testament Yes, well, God,
живут по ветхому завету Да ну Бог у
look
смотри
God, I understand correctly once again, the God of
Бог са я правильно понимаю ещё раз Бог у
Moses and your Russian nationalist are the
Моисея и у вас русского националиста
same. You are a
один и тот же самый Вы же вы же человек
Christian, I’m not a believer, I’m just
христианин я не верующий Я просто так
studying  religion I am a religious scholar
изучаю религию я религиовед теолог
theologian Yes theologian Yes, I graduated from
теолог Да теолог теолог да заканчивал
seminary, but I didn’t go on to work,
семинарию типа но не пошёл типа работать
that is, see the question From Moses
дальше то есть смотрите вопрос У Моисея
From Abraham and you, by the way, what is my name
У Авраама и у вас Вас кстати как зовут
Andrey Andrey Very nice My name is
Андрей Андрей Очень приятно Меня зовут
Herman from the city of Khmelnitsky I say
Герман из города Хмельницкий Я говорю
I’m 42 years old  you have Herman from
Мне 42 года получается у вас Герман у
Moses, who led people through the desert for 40 years.
Моисея который водил по пустыне 40 лет
Yes, Abraham has the same
людей Да У Авраама один и тот же самый
God,
Бог
right. Well, he has the same God. Well, you
правильно Ну Бог же он имеет он же Ну
know, as an outcome from Christian
знаете как изход из христианской
theology. Well,  Your God is the same
теологии Ну Бог у вас один и то же самы
Dawa, look, you and Muslims have a different
Дава смотри у вас и у мусульман разный
God, so you have Allah or
Бог вот у тебя Аллах или
not No, I don’t believe in Allah is different You
нет Нет я не верю в Аллаха разный Вот ты
don’t believe, yes, but you believe in the same
не веришь да но ты веришь в в того же
God that Moses believed
бога что и верил Моисей
in. True Well,  Moses didn’t believe in God
Правда Ну в Моисей не верил в Бога
Moses believed in the
Моисей Верил в
prophet let’s do this with Moses Who was the god
пророка давай так у Моисея Кто был богом
Yahweh Yahweh is the same
Яхве Яхве так тот же самый что
as
и
they believe that Jesus Christ is when there
нуде считают что вот Иисус Христос когда
will be a Second Coming what do they have
Ну будет Второе пришествие что у них
your Lord will come
придёт свой свой
Well, you need to understand more, but
Господь Ну вы больше разбирайтесь но тем
nevertheless, Well, for us it will be the Antichrist
не менее Ну Для нас это будет антихрист
again, look
ещё раз смотри
about the prophets, this is already the second level, here I
вот про пророков это уже второй уровень
look at the top level That is, you get
вот верхнем уровне смотрю То есть у вас
God the son Jesus Christ God the
получается Бог сын Иисус Христос Бог
father of Yahweh, so it turns out He is the same
отец Яхве так так же получается Он же
sent his son not Jesus is also
послал своего сына не Иисус тоже на
actually one of the prophets so and so if like
самом деле один из пророков так-то если
this with yes yes Well that's right But with the
вот так с да да Ну правильно А вот с
father the father What is the name of the father the name of God which is the
отец отец Как имя отца имя Бога который
father of Jesus the name of
отец Иисуса имя
god damn listen Well he's Yahweh he's the
бо блин слушайте Ну он же Яхве он же
Savov he  same elom Yahweh is in Judaism You
савов он же элом Яхве это в иудаизме Вы
have it Open look in the new testament
имеете это Открой смотри в новом завете
Open and you will see how many words of
Открой и ты сколько увидишь слов
Yahweh I will see yes right yes that is look it
Яхве увижу да право да то есть смотри
turns out that
получается что
you are a Russian nationalist praying to the
ты русский националист молишься
Jewish God I don’t pray to the Jewish
еврейскому Богу я не молюсь еврейскому
God you understand God he is One Yes but
Богу понимаете бог он Един Да но
for some reason  he has the Hebrew name Yahweh and
почему-то он с именем еврейским Яхве а
not, for example, there is Dibor, well damn Well,
не например там дибор ну блин Ну тем не
nevertheless, you know how, well, wait, wait,
менее знаете как ну подожди подожди как
how is that me here
тем ме вот сри
we are  Russian Slavic
нро наши русские славянские
gods are with you now. You can also
боги сечас с вами Вот вы можете тоже там
talk about your topic there and live there. I
разговаривать поживать У меня
really, well, that is,
действительно Ну то есть
in
на
our name, he simply
нас именном
believed. That is, how would I
уверовал просто То есть как бы я раньше
have been a pagan myself before? I don’t believe I believe that
был сам язычник я ве не я верю верю что
you believed Yes, I’m just wondering  that
ты уверовал Да мне просто интересно то
is, it turns out that you believe You are a Russian
есть ты получается уверовал Ты русский
nationalist but you believe in the Jewish
националист но веришь в еврейского
national God Yes, I believe in the
национального Бога Да я верю в
Jewish national God, so
еврейского национального Бога пусть Вам
be it as you please Yes Yes, it’s easier for me this way
Вам так будет угодно Да Да мне так легче
Yes, it’s interesting I love this stuff from
Да интересно Я люблю вот это там у
Russian nationalists  This is such a
русских националистов Вот это такое
discrepancy, I understood it interestingly Well, listen,
расхождение интересно понял Ну слушайте
damn Oh, he’s the Lord, he’s also the Fast For
ну блин О он же Господь он же Постол За
the sins of all people Yes, yes, yes Absolutely
грехи всех людей Да дада да Абсолютно
true Yes, and he said that in short,
верно Да и сказал что короче
I even Imagine now, 2000 years
Я даже Представьте сейчас вот 2000 лет
have passed, the 2nd
прошло 2
century, damn, I still feel in
век блин я тем не менее чувствую в
myself in  what's wrong with you so that well
себе в себе что с тем чтобы с тем чтобы
I'm a sinful person very very
ну я я греховный человек очень очень
bad And you just rolled
плохой А ты вот это только что накатил
this this is what you
это что ты
drank that well you rolled 100 rooks This is
выпил что ну ты накатил 100 грачиков Это
what you
что ты
didn't not a hundred  Loud You are wrong, not me, I’m
не не сто громка Вы не правы не я вот я
just drinking on stock
просто на стоку пью на стоку
what
чего
vodka I’m just instagram just tincture
водки Я просто инстагра просто настоечка
I’m Orthodox Orthodox for
ью православненько православненько за
Jesus it’s not something that it’s not that
Иисуса не то что то что не то что
Ukraine has lost the Lord it’s that Ukraine
Украина лишилась Господа то что Украина
has gone along the satanic path it’s a fact
пошла по сатанинском пути это факт то
that Ukraine will be  existence is also a fact
что Украина будет существовать тоже факт
Glorious country Yes, Ukraine is an
Славная страна Да Украина - это
Orthodox country And well, Ramzan
православная страна А хорошо э Рамзан
Kadyrov is an Orthodox
Кадыров православный
person Ramen cadres is not an Orthodox
человек Рамен кадров не православный
person Wait  and how do you
человек Подождите а как у вас в
get a non-
православной стране получается не
Orthodox
православные
order in an Orthodox country? We don’t have a multinational
порядки не у нас многонациональное
state. Yes, I understand, that means you have a non-
государство Да понял то есть у вас не
Orthodox state. Well,
православное значит государство Ну
the majority of Russian people, of course,
большинство русских людей конечно
Russian people always understand the Motherland, what do
русские люди всегда льно пони Родина что
you understand? In my
вы понимаете У меня
19th century, the Orthodox
19ст православного
Tsar renounced the
царя отреклись от веры
Orthodox faith according to  they threw down churches churches
православной по скидывали храмы церкви У
I just understand like, well,
меня просто понимаете типа ну у нас как
we have a chat, we have people fighting
у нас есть чат у нас вот люди есть воюют
for Ukraine, Lord for Well, reservist Sakha
за Украину Господи за Ну резервист Саха
for
за
Israel we support  Israel Who are you?
Израиль мы поддерживаем Израиль Кто вы
Well, I’m my own, I’m my friends, and so on My
Ну я свои я свои друзья и так далее Мой
father
отец
Supports we just have a friend there,
Поддерживает у нас там просто есть друг
we’re for Well, we’re kind of for him How can we
мы за Ну мы как бы за него Как мы можем
support Not ours, well, there’s your friends, I
поддерживать Не свого ну там свои друзья
understand, then you, in short, you’re a Russian
понял то ты короче ты русский
nationalist, you support Israel now
националист поддерживаешь Израиль сейчас
like that  of course, Putin supports Hamas
так конечно а Путин поддерживает Хамас
Yes, Putin doesn’t support anyone boor
Да Путин никого не поддерживает хама
does this will happen and Putin is a Russian
делает такого выйдет а Путин он русский
nationalist or not
националист или не
Russian Putin a multinational
русский Путин многонациональный
nationalist understood a multinational
националист понял многонациональный
nationalist No matter how
националист Как бы как бы то ни было не
strange it may sound Putin himself said a
звучало странно Путин сам сказал
multinational nation  You understand,
многонациональная нация Сами понимаете
this is such a dialectic. Yes, how is it?
оня это такая диалектика Да как вот это
I don’t understand what you think, we ourselves
я не понимаю что вы думаете мы сами
understand what kind of dialectic this is. Well, look,
понимаем что это за диалектика Ну смотри
if you understood that God is three and One, then
если если ты понял что бог три Един то
why couldn’t you understand that the Russian
почему ты не мог понять что русская
nation is
нация
multinational? No, damn, Russian
многонациональна Не ну ну блин русские
people are actually
люди чно
Well, look God, he’s like God the father God the son and
Ну смотри бог он типа Бог отец Бог сын и
God the Holy Spirit this is the Russians the youngster
Бог Святой Дух это россияне тенец
Russian Russian Russian Russian there
россиянин русский россиянин там
Belarusian and so Yes, I understand the Russians
белорусский и так Да я понял россияне
Well, you know, the Russians are also different, they are
Ну знаете россияне тоже разные бывают
different I
разные
understand
понял
Uh-huh  And this is what you Russian
Угу А вот чем Вот вы русские
nationalists are doing besides four
националисты занимаетесь кроме чет
roulettes,
рулетки
here we support the Russian national
вот мы поддерживаем русскую национальную
idea in telegram,
идею в телеграме
support the Russian national idea in
поддержите русско национальную идею в
telegra, you know ru Russian in general, you
телегра знаете ру русская вообще на Зов
can subscribe to the Call, in fact, we are
можете подписаться на самом деле мы
against the ethnic lawlessness of ethnic
против этнического беспредела этнических
bans We have a very problem in Russia
бан У нас есть в России есть проблема
Look, besides the telegram, you
очень очень смотри кроме телеграма у вас
have some kind of activity, of course I’m
какая-то деятельность есть конечно Я же
telling you, like we have a
вам говорю типа у нас
very big problem in terms of migration
очень большая проблема в плане миграции
in terms of ethnic gangs, what people I
в плане этнических Банд то что люди я
know about what migration is  for example
знаю о чём миграци например
Zhizhi Yes, tell us Well, we have a
Жижи Да расскажи Ну у на у нас есть
group on Telegram, the Russian community
группа в телеграме русская община
understood the call. Well, listen, in our country,
поняли Ну слушайте у нас в стране
you understand. In our country, it is
понимаете У нас в стране
promoted, that is, not also Friendship of
пропагандируется то есть не тоже Дружба
Peoples, but some kind of
народов но какая-то
well, that is, in Na, too, there is
некая ну то есть у на тоже есть
uncontrolled migration
бесконтрольная миграция
and  different people really Well,
и разные люди действительно Ну
they let people through who even
пропускают людей которые даже Люде
deport Luda back, well, from Russia they
депортируют обратно ну из России
return people back to us, there are people who are
возвращают обратно к нам люди есть
generally inadequate, that is, they form
неадекватные вообще то есть составляют
their own Well, ethnic
свои Ну этнические
groups How old are you, by the way 22
группировки А тебе сколько лет кстати 22
22 How many children do you have zero and how many children does an ethnic migrant have at 22 years old I don’t keep track of them And at least you have a girlfriend there, some kind of Russian Ukrainian Well, like Slavyanka Slavyanka what was Slavyanka is there is Slavyanka yes I always feel like I didn’t have a problem, I have a girl I know from Kyiv, a very kind girl from Kyiv. Well, we talked to her here, let’s put it this way  Moscow Well, she’s
общались здесь скажем так Москве Ну она
there, well, she’s very not, she’s very pro
там ну она очень не она очень про
Ukrainian girl, but damn, she’s cool,
украинская девчонка ти но блин крутая
really cool, and there’s a girl who’s
реально крутая и есть девчонка которая
pro Ukrainian here, she’s just like,
про украинская здесь она прям вот вот
damn, this happens to me all the time. Yeah,
блин вот постоянно у меня так бывает Угу
for some reason, a very exotic let’s say
почему-то очень экзотическим скажем так
option Why why with you  Your
вариантом Почему почему у тебя У тебя
parents are also Russian. As I understand it,
родители же тоже русские Я так понимаю
they were. Well, my father was born in Rostov
были Ну у меня ме родилась в Ростове
in the Krasnodar Territory, so
отец в Краснодарском крае чего они тебя
out of fear they named you Herman Ani there
с перепуга назвали Герман Ани там
Evlampy
Евлампий
Ioan I don’t know, to be honest,
Иоан не знаю честно сказать исконно
I don’t know, I can’t
русскими именами не не знаю я не могу
say well, but for example,
сказать хорошо а вот например
your last name is Russian or not Russian,
твоя фамилия она русская или не русская
so your last name is Shamraev, yes, it’s
вот у тебя она шамраев фамилия да Это
clearly not
явно не
Russian, you know, the problem there is that
русская понимаете там проблема в том что
you want to sign the Chechens, but after all
вы хотите Ну подписать чеченов Но ведь
all the surnames are Chechen, they were
все фамилии чеченские они русифицирован
originally Russified Well, go shamraev, this is most
изначально Ну поди шамраев это скоре
likely on behalf of some kind of Turkic
всего от имени тюркского какого-то
shamray Yes no In fact, if we
шамрай Да нет На самом деле если мым
google shamrai shamrai Yes, you are right, in
гуглить шамрай шамрай Да вы право на
fact, there is also a Tatar Well, part
самом деле тоже Татарская есть Ну часть
And if there is such a name, more precisely the word
А если есть такое имя точнее слово
shamrai is a Ukrainian word. Although
шамрай - это украинское слово Хотя
it would seem that
Казалось
there is such a village as Shara Obla, from the
бы есть такая деревня шара обла вот от
White Church, I’m actually in Polish
бело церкви я вот реально польском
Ukrainian there is shamrai, but you got away with it,
украинском есть шамрай да отмазался ты
you’re
тебе
lucky  yes but look if you were
повезло да но смотри если бы ты был
Polish Ukrainian you would be either shamray
польский украинский ты был или бы шамрай
or or
или или
sha I have a lot of Poles, in fact,
ша У меня много Поляков на самом деле
too,
тоже
you already We have you  found a little Well,
есть ты уже Мы тебя немножко
listen Nunu, many Russians
нашли Ну слушайте нуну у многих русских
have Poles, in fact I understood yes Well,
есть поляки на самом деле понял да А ну
it’s a very intimate question and there are no Jews in my
так очень интимный вопрос а евреев в
family
роду
and I
нету нету а
don’t
немцев не
know any Germans Well, you don’t know, I don’t know
знаю Ну как не знаешь не знаю
there were some Dagestanis, Chechens in the
были какие-то дагестанцы чеченцы в
Rada
Раду
no, I just know  there, well, great-grandfathers,
нет Вот я просто знаю там ну прадедушек
great-grandmothers, and so on, I understood, yes, okay,
прабабушек и так далее понял да хорошо а
but look, I understand correctly that
вот смотри я правильно что понимаю что
you are a
ты
representative of a subculture there or like a
представитель субкультуры там или как
movement Yes, which has already held Russian
движения Да которое проводило русские
marches,
марши
marches already Yes, well, you held  Well, these are your
маршев уже Да ну вы проводили это ж Ваши
Russian nationalists or
русские националисты или
not, you know, the Russian ma Dmitry Demushkin carried out,
нет понимаете проводил русский ма
in short, everyone there
пон короче там все
was absolutely about the Ukrainian Dude,
проводили абсолютно про украинский Чувак
now he’s about the Ukrainian about the Ukrainian
сейчас он про украинский про украинский
Yes, let’s just say he’s not so much about the
Да скажем так он не столько про
Ukrainian, he’s anti-war, like he’s burning
украинский он антивоенный типа он горит
in the
во
Russian
русской
nation, Dmit Demushkin is a traitor and  the
нации дмит демушкин - это предатель и
enemy is a traitor
враг предатель
to the Russians. What is he saying that’s so bad?
кого русских А что он такого плохого
It’s interesting, I read Mishkin and
говорит вот интересно я читал Мишкина и
watched his programs, what does he say
смотрел его передачи что он говорит
against the Russians?  Dmitry Dyomushkin
такого против русских Дмитрий дёмушкин
absolutely Because if Russia, if
абсолютно Потому что если Россия если
Russia loses Donbass, if Russia
Россия потеряет Донбасс если Россия
loses all the territories it captured, let’s say,
потеряет все захваченные скажем так
then this means the loss of
территории то это означает потерю
Russian identity, this means the collapse of
русской идентичности это означает развал
Russia, dude, don’t you think it’s a
России чувак Тебе не кажется Тебе не
loss, don’t you think that’s a
кажется что вот потеря то что Короче вы
loss?  Russian is identical,
полноценно это потеря русской идентично
you, as a Ukrainian nationalist, still
вы как украинский националист всё-таки
must also understand that well, Russia
тоже должны понимать что ну Россия
looks at you, come on, tell me, I’m interested,
Смотри Давай расскажи мне интересно
Ukraine won’t let’s say let’s say, and it’s
Украина вону Допустим Допустим и
good for us, you’re Russian nationalists. What
хорошо нам вы русские националисты Что
you can be ruled by the Chechens in Russia,
можете в России вас правят чеченцы
in short, by anyone Yes, but not by
короче кто угодно Да но не
you, why the hell did this guy
Вы почему сри намер вот этот парень
know Nikita Zhuravel, whose son
знаешь Никита Журавель которого сын
Kadyrov is great, and that one of you
Кадырова прекрасно и что кто-то из вас
defended Nikita Zhuravel, even in
защитил Никиту журавля хоть в
a telegram, the floor is
телеграме пол
sad, like you can’t do that, you can’t
печальный типа нельзя так делать нельзя
do it, like he did  there's
сделать он типа сделал там
a fool there Yes, there is a law, yes According to what
дуро Да есть за есть закон да По какому
law they took him, they gave him away, not work according to
закону его взяли отдали не работа по
some kind of methodology, definitely to Chechnya,
методике какой-то определённо в Чечню
they took him on camera just because it’s harsh
забрали на камеру просто так что жесть
Yes, they also gave him  Order to this little
Да вот ещё эти дали орден малому этому
Kadyrov Yes, for the fact that he
Кадырову Да за то что он первого
beat the first Russian at the age of 15 and that’s what you
русского побил в 15 лет и вот и что вы
Russian nationalists all over Russia
русские националисты по всей России
did. You just say
сделали Вот вы просто говорите
DTD three, don’t just tell me how you, as a
дтд три не просто вот скажи как ты как
Russian nationalist, supported Nikita
русский националист поддержал Никиту
the Crane. Well, wait Nikita
журавля Ну подождите Никита
Zhuravel Zhuravel You  you also think
Журавель Журавель Вы тоже считаете
Parker turns out Lex I keep reading
паркера получается Лекс Я всё читаю у
I have such a Parker then be good we
меня такая паркера то быть добру мы всех
respect everyone good yes come on yes be good I
уважаем добру да давай да быть добру я
understand listen Well  damn, we don’t
понял слушайте Ну блин мы не
support this, well, wait, you
поддерживаем это да ну подождите вы его
didn’t protect him, they beat him, it shows on
не защитили его бьют это показывает на
camera how a Chechen mocks a
камеру как чеченец издевается над
Russian, Kadyrov’s son, a minor, beats a
русским сын Кадырова малолетний избивает
Russian guy like damn, like some kind of woman, and
русского парня как блин как какую-то и
what did you do?
что вы сделали Не ну он сбивает тоже как
obviously and also confuses the question How
очевидно и тоже сбивает вопрос Как
he beats, beats from the knee or from
избивает избивает с колена короче бли с
the butt You
приклада Ты же
saw Yes and especially We saw how Kadyrov’s son
видел Да и особенно Мы видели как сын
later Yes Like him it Look then not
потом Да Типа ему это Смотри потом не
later  before that, I also participated again,
потом до этого тоже участвовал ещё раз
look, your Russian guy, maybe
смотри вот вашего русского парня может
he did something wrong, the Chechens
он сделал что-то неправильно чеченцы
took him to a pre-trial detention center and just beat him like a toy
забрали в СИЗО и просто как игрушку
and show that
лупят и показывают что
they are humiliating, beating, what did you do, that’s
они унижают избивают что вы сделали вот
all Misha Misha Mavashi is yours, in short, that’s
все Миша Миша Маваши ваш ты короче вот
all Please tell me how it is  influences
все Скажите пожалуйста как это влияет на
the bombing of Ukraine and the
бомбардировку Украины причём
bombing of Ukraine I say that you are
бомбардировка Украины Я говорю что вы
you Well, your in the Russian Federation
вас Ну сри ваш в Российской Федерации
How does it affect How does it affect when I
Как это влияет Как это влияет на при обю
explain that you Why you  you are interested,
объясняю что вы Почему вы интересуетесь
both look Because you are a Russian
обя смотри Потому что ты русский
nationalist Yes, how are you doing?
националист Да как ты себя при Ты никто
You are no one in Russia, in short, tomorrow Ramzan
в России тебя короче завтра Рамзан
Kadyrov will say Shut up your darlings from the
Кадыров скажет Заткни своё няшки из
information field, this will not happen, and the
информационное поле такого не будет а
information field is as good as your
информационное поле так хорошо как ваше
information field helped Nikita
информационное поле помогло Никиту
Nikita so that his son does not read him  Ramzan
Никите жв чтобы его не чил сын Рамзана
Kadyrov
Кадырова
is a lawlessness, we don’t argue with you as
это беспредел мы с вами не спорим так
correctly as you prevent this
правильно как вы препятствует этому
lawlessness, how you cheated, went to
беспределу как вы изменили вышли на
a rally, said
митинг сказали
Kadyrov, get out of our Earth, Let
Кадыров пшёл вон с нашей Земли Отпусти
our Russian go  what did you do or
нашего русского что вы сделали или
cry on the telegram I’m not arguing with you
поплакали в телеграме я с тобой не спорю
I’m not arguing with you Well, that is, you
я с тобой не спорю Ну то есть ты
admit that you are all Russian
признаёшь что вы все российские
nationalists who are now
националисты которые вот сейчас мы
bombing Ukraine
бомбим Украину
All of you cannot protect one
Всё вы не можете защитить одного
Russian guy in Russia,
русского парня в России
but it turns out
да получается
like this Live now Sati Slava  Ukra Well
так Живи теперь Сати Слава Укра Ну
Live Glory to Ukraine
Живите Слава Украине
Yaks Just a
яки Просто
crappy Russian
капец русски
nationalist here we are leading this Russian
националист мы тут мы ведём русскую эту
in
в
[laughter]
[смех]
telegram So they give you stars not in the
телеграме Так звездюлей вам дают не в
telegram but in
телеграме а в
Instagram,
Инстаграме
if you know
бли такой знаете
him, this sad face at the end is
его это печальное лицо в конце это
just such a beauty Well, it turns out he’s
просто тако кра Ну да получается
sitting like that. They’re really sitting there,
так сидит Вот они там реально сидят
just downcast and powerless, and
такие опущенные просто да бесправные да
they’re just being mocked, they’re already being driven out by
над ними просто издеваются уже гонят
Kadyrov, he’s just counting
Кадыров просто их как считает Да смеётся
them. Yes, he’s laughing at them, like, yes, and this one is us  there you are there to You're
с них типа да А этот мы там вас там к Ты
just you're pathetic pathetic you just
просто ты жалкий жалкий просто знаешь
know, I don't know if there are any dating
вот я не знаю есть какие-то встречаются
They at least have some kind of pride there you
Они хоть какую-то имеют там гордость ты
damn how you should not respect yourself
блин как нужно себя не уважать Просто
It's just crap I have no words  subscribe to the
капец это у меня нет слов подпишитесь на
channel Yes Like and comment
канал Да Поставьте лайк залиште комент
what do you think about this video Glory to
что вы думаете про це видео Слава
Ukraine Write to my Telegram directly at once axis of
Украине Пиши на мий Telegram прямо зараз
wine and
ось вин а
popk this is very and very important YouTube taking
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the scum of ODS in your ban and I do
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
n’t show too much video to people at all times I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show it  information about the stream For this purpose,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
you need to write directly to Mali for the operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
now and in the meantime there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video sche tezh tsikava and korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will
информация и мы пон вами трима постийний
show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
YouTube Слава Украине пиши